daddiesboardshop.com 2019-04-22

# Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy  
effective date: June 7, 2018

This privacy policy has two parts. A first part, entitled "Daddies Board Shop Privacy Policy”, is applicable to the entire Daddies Board Shop website located at dadiesboardshop.com, with the exception of the Daddies Wood Shop website, located at daddiesboardshop.com/woodshop. A second part, entitled "Daddies Wood Shop Privacy Policy”, is applicable solely to the Daddies Wood Shop website located at daddiesboardshop.com/woodshop.

Daddies Board Shop Privacy Policy

Protecting your privacy is a top priority to us. We are in the business of selling skateboard and snowboard gear, not names or personal information. Daddiesboardshop.com has created this privacy policy in order to disclose our information gathering and dissemination practices for this web site. In particular, this Privacy Policy describes our privacy practices with regard to information about you that could reasonably be used to identify you personally or that is associated with information that identifies you (“Personal Information”) 

What we collect and how it is used: 

We may collect your name, address and phone number. We will need this information to complete and process your order. This information is viewed only by the owners and employees of daddiesboardshop.com if they are involved in the completion, delivery or customer support of your order. How this information is used: The order is processed and kept in our confidential files for record-keeping purposes. All paper data is destroyed via Docu-Shred on a bi-monthly basis. Personal Information may be disclosed to trusted persons working together with Daddies if they are involved in the completion, delivery or customer support of your order of goods and/or services offered through the websites. Examples include third parties who are providing the goods and/or services offered through the websites, assist in hosting our web servers, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, sales tracking, processing credit card or other forms of payments, and providing customer service. We also may share aggregated anonymous information about visitors to our websites with third parties so that they can understand the kinds of visitors to the websites and how those visitors use the websites.

We may disclose and transfer such information to a third party who acquires all or a substantial portion of our business, whether such acquisition is by way of merger, consolidation or purchase of all or a substantial portion of our assets. In addition, in the event we become the subject of an insolvency proceeding, whether voluntary or involuntary, we or our liquidator, administrator, receiver or administrative receiver may sell, license or otherwise dispose of such information in a transaction approved by the court.

By logging into the Daddies websites, or expressly opting in when presented with choices, you have consented for us to use your information, subject to local law, in at least the following ways: to create a profile for you based on information that you have provided to us; to contact you about any Daddies’ website updates, informational and service-related communications, including important security updates; to provide you additional communications, information, and promotions such as newsletters; to inform you of other products or services available from Daddies or its affiliates; to provide the services requested by you; to enable you to provide feedback, to contact us and for us to respond to you; and to generate internal reports about the use of our websites.

We may also share your information to carefully-selected third parties, if you consent to such disclosure so that they may inform you of offers, promotions and services.

We also collect login information used to access Daddies’ websites. You are responsible for ensuring that your log-in information (e.g., your User ID and password) are kept confidential. We have implemented technical and organizational measures designed to secure your Personal Information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration or disclosure. Notwithstanding such measures, the Internet is an open system and we cannot guarantee that unauthorized third parties will never be able to defeat those measures or use your Personal Information for improper purposes. Please consider this prior to submitting your Personal Information to us via our websites.

We may also allow other companies to display advertisements to you while you are visiting our websites. Because your Web browser must request these advertisements from the other companies’ servers, these companies can view, edit or set their own cookies, just as if you had requested a webpage from their site. Daddies has no control over, and is not responsible for, the practices of those third party advertisers and encourages you to review the policies of such advertisers. 

We may allow third party cookies as part of online advertising campaigns to determine and track site traffic landing from Daddies’ advertising banners that have been placed on the websites of third parties. The data collected via these cookies is anonymous and the information is not linked to your personally identifiable information without your permission.

Posting Your Information to Public Areas of the Site. We do not display Personal Information without your permission. However, if you post any of your Personal Information in public areas of our websites, such as in product or service reviews, online forums or chat rooms, such information may be collected and used by others over whom we have no control. We cannot control the use made by third parties of information you post or otherwise make available in public areas of our websites.

Credit Card information. Your credit card is charged as you submit your order only for the amount you have approved. Refunds for returned products or unavailable items are processed with the same credit card that was provided in the original order. At no point does Daddies Board Shop possess the full credit card number unless given to it during a manual transaction, such as a phone order. A short period of time after the order is processed, the credit card information is purged from the order. 

Email address and phone number. We require your e-mail address and phone number to contact you if we have a question regarding your order. This information may be disclosed to trusted persons working together with daddiesboardshop.com if they are involved in the completion, delivery or customer support of your order. We will NEVER call your phone number if it is not related to your order. How this information is used: Customers that place an order may receive notifications of new arrivals, discounts and updated information from our web site. You may "Opt Out" of receiving these emails by using the "Unsubscribe Me" link at the bottom of every e-mail. Customer Service may also use your email address to contact you about abandoned shopping carts or uncompleted orders. 

Cookies. Cookies are a message that a web server transmits to a web browser to personalize the user's experience on our web site. Cookies can help store personal information about you so that when you return to the site you have a more personalized experience. Have you ever returned to a site and have seen your name mysteriously appear on the screen? It is because on a previous visit you gave your name to the site and it was stored in a cookie so that when you returned you would be greeted with a personal message. Cookies do not act maliciously on computer systems. They are merely text files that you have the option of deleting at any time. All browsers can be set to reject cookies if the user prefers to use the Internet without enabling cookies to be stored. Please note that certain features of the check out process may require you to enable Cookies on your browser. 

Changes/Modifications. You may have access to, review, correct, update, restrict the use of, change or delete your account profile information or other Personal Information with us at any time. Such steps may be done by logging into the websites and following the instructions therein, if available, or by contacting us at help@daddiesboardshop.com. You also may obtain, upon request, the Personal Information you provided to us in a structured, commonly-used and machine-readable format. Before providing you with a copy of your Personal Information or correcting, updating or deleting such information, we reserve the right to verify and authenticate your identity and the Personal Information to which you have requested access. 

If you delete or close your account or account profile information with us altogether, we may retain an archival copy which is not accessible by you or third parties on the Internet. The archival copy is retained only for as long as we reasonably consider necessary for audit and record purposes. We will retain logs, demographic, indirect, and statistical information about you and keep an archival copy of this information in an anonymous form. If your Personal Information was previously accessed by others using our websites, we are not able to delete the information or copies thereof from their systems.

How Long We Keep Personal Information. Typically, we keep Personal Information for the length of any contractual relationship and, to the extent permitted by applicable laws, after the end of that relationship for as long as necessary to perform purposes set out in this Privacy Policy, to protect us from legal claims and administer our business. When we no longer need to use Personal Information, we will delete it from our systems and records or take steps to anonymize the data unless we need to keep it longer to comply with a legal or regulatory obligation.

Your European and California Rights. We do not share Personal Information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes unless you affirmatively agree to, or opt in to, such disclosure. California customers may request further information about our compliance with California laws by e-mailing us at help@daddiesboardshop.com. Please note that we are only required to respond to one request per customer each year, and we are not required to respond to requests made by means other than through this e-mail address.

In accordance with Article 77 of the General Data Protection Regulation, Europeans also have the right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority, in particular in the Member State of your habitual residence, place of work or of an alleged infringement of the GDPR. Our collection, storage and use of your Personal Information, and the processing by a Processor of your Personal Information, shall be governed by the Privacy Policy and, for residents of EU members states, the GDPR.

Third Party Interaction. As a user of the Daddies’ websites, you may interact with, purchase goods and/or services, or participate in promotions of advertisers, members, partners, or sponsors showing their goods and/or services on the websites. Unless otherwise stated, any such interaction, purchase or promotion, including the delivery of and the payment for goods and/or services, and any other term, condition, warranty or representation associated with such correspondence, purchase or promotion, is solely between you and the applicable third party. You agree that Daddies, its subsidiaries, affiliates, officers, agents, co-branders or other partners, and employees have no liability, obligation or responsibility for any such interaction, purchase or promotion between you and any such third party.

Legal Disclosure

We reserve the right to monitor, and disclose to, government officials or law enforcement, without your consent, any communications and personally identifiable information, whenever prompted to do so by legal authorities, even when you have requested that your information not be disclosed to third parties. Any rights not expressly granted herein are reserved. The contents of daddiesboardshop.com are provided "AS IS" and may contain errors or inaccuracies and may not be complete or current (we strive for 100% accuracy but we are only human). We reserve the right to correct any errors, inaccuracies or omissions (including after an order has been submitted) and to modify, change or update information (including pricing and/or product code numbers), at any time without prior notice. We may terminate your access or suspend your right to access to all or part of daddiesboardshop.com, without notice, for any conduct that we believe is in violation of any applicable law or is harmful to the interests of our web site. We reserve the right to change this policy at any time and will post any changes to this policy on their effective date. 

Daddies Wood Shop Privacy Policy

Daddies Board Shop, LLC ("Daddies”) owns and provides the Daddies Wood Shop website located at daddiesboardshop.com/woodshop (the "Network”). Please read this Privacy Policy carefully because it governs your use of the Network and services accessible via the website, collectively the "Services.” This Privacy Policy pertains to the Daddies Wood Shop. 

Summary  
The Privacy Policy explains what information is collected and how it is used. Your privacy is important and the goal of this Privacy Policy is to be as simple and non-technical as possible. 

What Information is Collected and How

Technical information is collected when you interact with the Network  
Like almost all websites or mobile applications, the Network may create and record certain information in an automated way. For example, when you use the Network, its servers may automatically record information about your interaction with its products ("Log Data”), including information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website. Log Data may include the address of the web page you were visiting before you came to the Network, your Internet Protocol address, the date and time of your request, browser type and settings, and how you interacted with the Network. 

The Network may also use "cookies” (a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes), or similar technologies to record Log Data. When cookies are used, the Network may use "session” cookies (that last until you close your browser) or "persistent” cookies (that last until you or your browser delete them). For example, the Network may use cookies to store your language preferences or other Network settings so you don’t have to set them up every time you visit the Network. 

The Network may also collect information about the device you’re using when accessing the Network, including what type of device it is, what operating system you’re using, device settings, unique device identifiers, and crash data. Whether the Network collects some or all of this information often depends on what type of device you’re using and its settings. For example, different types of information are available depending on whether you’re using a Mac or a PC, or an iPhone or an Android phone. To learn more about what information your device makes available, please also check the policies of your device manufacturer or software provider. 

Information is collected when you give it, or give permission to collect it  
When you sign up for or use the Network’s Services, you may voluntarily share certain information. This can include information such as your name, profile photo, comments, email address, and any other information you provide. 

How Information is Used  
Information collected is used to provide the Services to you and make them better, develop new Services, and protect the Network and its users. 

The information collected may be "personally identifiable” (meaning it can be used to specifically identify you as a unique person) or "non-personally identifiable” (meaning it can’t be used to specifically identify you). The Network uses both types of information, and combinations of both types, as described above. 

Daddies also may disclose personal information about you, without notice: (i) in response to requests from local, state or federal law enforcement officials; (ii) if requested by any judicial, administrative or similar proceeding or order, such as a subpoena; or (iii) if otherwise required by law. 

How Information is Shared  
If you provide the Network with personal information, that information may be used to alert you of new products or services, features, or enhancements; handle your customer service questions or issues; request feedback; and notify you of promotions, updates, or special offers that may interest you. Daddies reserves the right to offer third party services and products to you based on the information that you supply and the preferences that you identify in your registration and at any time thereafter; such offers may be made by Daddies or by third parties. 

Your personal information may be used with non-personal information that was collected in a manner such that the end-product does not personally identify you or any other user. Your personal information may be made non-personally identifiable by either combining it with information about other users (aggregating your personal information with information about other users), or by removing characteristics (such as your name or email address) that make the information personally identifiable. This process is known as de-personalizing your information. You grant Daddies a royalty-free, worldwide, perpetual, irrevocable and fully transferable right and license to use your personal information in connection with the creation and development of analytical and statistical analysis tools relating to the use of the customer data collected (the "Analytical Data”). 

Children’s Privacy  
The Network is not intended for children under 16, and personal information from children under 16 will not knowingly be collected. Children’s privacy is a serious matter and parents are encouraged to play an active role in their children’s online experience at all times. 

Consent  
By using the Network, you consent to the collection and use of this information by the Network. 

Notification of Changes  
This Privacy Policy may change from time to time and all such changes will be posted on this page. 

Terms of Use  
Please read the Terms of Service governing the use of the Network.
